Preliminary Inventory to the Charles Schuveldt Dewey Papers, 1897-1942
Hoover Institution Archives
Charles Schuveldt Dewey Papers,
1897-1942
82017
Dewey, Charles Schuveldt, 1880-1980
18 oversize boxes (7.5 linear feet)
Hoover Institution Archives Stanford, California 94305-6010
Clippings, letters, speeches and writings, press releases, printed matter, photographs, and memorabilia, relating to Polish finances, and to American politics.
Administrative Information
Access
Collection open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Access Points
Finance, Public--Poland; Finance, Public--United States; Poland; Poland--Economic conditions; United States--Politics and government; United States--Foreign relations; United States--Politics and government--20th century; Statesmen--United States
Container List
- Youth, 1897-1905 (Box 1)
- U.S. Assistant Secretary of the Treasury (Box 2)
  - 1924-1925
  - 1925-1926 (Box 3)
  - 1926-1927 (Box 4)
- Financial Advisor to Poland (Box 5)
  - 1927-1928
  - 1928 (Box 6-8)
  - 1929 (Box 9-10)
  - 1930 (Box 11-12)
- Private life, Chicago (Box 13)
  - 1931
  - 1932 (Box 14)
  - 1933-1934 (Box 15)
  - 1934-1938 (Box 16)
- U.S. Congress (Box 17)
  - 1938-1941
  - 1941-1942 (Box 18)